A Guide to the Records of the Virginia 350th Anniversary Commission, 1953-1958 (bulk 1954-1957)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. General files, 1953-1958., Extent: 33 boxes. (Box 1-33)
  - Special Days: Old Point Comfort Celebration, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Special Days: Old Point Comfort Celebration, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Special Days: Opening Ceremonies, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Special Days: Opening Ceremonies, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Special Days: Opening Ceremonies: Congressional Invitations, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Special Days: Polish Falcons of America, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Special Days: Proposed Washington Visit, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Special Days: Royal Dominion, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Special Days: Seventeenth Century Historical Symposium, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Special Days: Ship Christening Ceremony, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Special Days: Sixth Annual Legislative Work Conference on Southern Regional Education, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Special Days: St. Luke's Church, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Special Days: Virginia Area Days, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Special Days: Virginia Area Days, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Special Days: Virginia Polytechnic Institute Day, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day, 1953-1957 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Alexander Hamilton Bicentennial, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Centennial Legion, 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Centennial Legion, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Centennial Legion, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Centennial Legion, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Entertainment, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Fife and Drum Corps, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Fife and Drum Corps, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: General Program, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Invitations, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Invitations, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Military Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Physical Arrangements, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Physical Arrangements, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Yorktown Day Association, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Special Days: Yorktown Day: Yorktown Day Association, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Special Events, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Special Events, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Special Events, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Special Events, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Special Events, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Special Events, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Special Events, 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Special Events, 1955-1957 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Special Events: National Folk Festival, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Special Events: National Folk Festival, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Special Events: Programs and Brochures, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1954-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Speech Outline, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Staff Memos, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Standard Oil of New Jersey, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Stanley, Thomas B. (Governor), 1956 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - State Chamber of Commerce, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - State Conservation Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - State Highway, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - State House, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - State House, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - State House, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - State House: Design (H.C. Forman), 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - State House: Design (H.C. Forman), 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Statement of Responsibilities, 1955-1957 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - State Program: Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Stuart, Sir Campbell, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Student Union Building, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Tax Exemption, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Techniques: Art, 1954-1956 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Thalhimer's, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Three-hundreth Anniversary (1907), 1954-1957 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Traffic Survey, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Traffic Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Traffic Survey, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Travel: Railroads, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Travel: Water, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Un-American Organizations, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - University of Virginia Documents, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Hotel Association, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Press Association, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 350th Anniversary Celebration Corportation, 1954-1957 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 350th Anniversary Celebration Corporation, 1954-1957 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Regional Participation, 1954-1957 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties, Accomack - Brunswick, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Buckingham - Colonial Heights, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Cumberland - Greensville, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Halifax - James City, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: King and Queen - Mathews, 1955-1957 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Mecklenburg - Newport News, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Norfolk - Petersburg, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Pittsylvania - Rappahannock, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Richmond (City), 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Roanoke (City), 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Roanoke (County) - Wythe, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Institutions, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Regional Participation: Schools, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Travel Council, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Visitor Accomodations, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Visuals, 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Whaley, Emily, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Whittet and Shepperson, 1955-1956 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Whittet and Shepperson, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Oversize Material (Box 33)
  - Sketches of restaurant design (from Bids: Food folder) (Folder 1)
  - Tour booklet (from Commemorative Visit: Material Taken by Mr. Rouse folder) (Folder 2)
  - Map of Hampton Roads area (from Committee: Highway Beautification folder) (Folder 3)
  - Sketches of exhibits (from Exhibits: Miscellaneous folder) (Folder 4)
  - Advertisement (from Flags folder) (Folder 5)
  - Drawings of first aid, police headquarters and conduit layout of the park (from Glasshouse Point folder) (Folder 6)
  - Foundation plan (from Green Spring: Design folder) (Folder 7)
  - Map showing Virginia counties (from Housing folder) (Folder 8)
  - Richmond Times-Dispatch advertisement (from Musical and Dramatic Events folder) (Folder 9)
  - Illustrated maps of Colonial Williamsburg (from Plans: Colonial Williamsburg folder) (Folder 10)
  - Plat of Williamsburg (from Plans: Williamsburg City folder) (Folder 11)
  - Event program (from Queen's Visit: Service at Jamestown Island folder) (Folder 12)
  - Silk Stockings movie publicity poster (from Special Days: International Naval Review folder) (Folder 13)
  - Map of Yorktown Battlefield with seating chart on back (from Special Days: Yorktown Day: General Program folder) (Folder 14)
  - Drawing of State House (from State House: Design folder) (Folder 15)
  - Poster for Jamestown Festival Week in Amherst County (from Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Accomack-Brunswick folder) (Folder 16)
  - The Free Lance-Star Jamestown Week souvenir edition newspaper (from Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Cumberland-Greensville folder) (Folder 17)
  - Map of colonial Rappahannock (from Virginia Regional Participation: Cities and Counties: Pittsylvania-Rappahannock folder) (Folder 18)
- Oversize Material (Map Case 24)
  - Grading and layout plan for bridge under Tazewell Avenue (from Colonial National Historical Park folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 1)
  - Plans for providing ship anchorage (from Docking of Ships folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 2)
  - Road map of Williamsburg (from Festival Information Center folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 3)
  - Plat/survey of armory site (from Festival Information Center folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 3)
  - Architectural drawing of service station building (from Glasshouse Point folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 4)
  - Map of Williamsburg (from Plans: Armory folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - Architectural drawing of National Guard armory (from Plans: Armory folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary survey of proposed armory site (from Plans: Armory folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary plat of land for armory (from Plans: Armory folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - General interpretive plan for Jamestown Island (from Plans: Jamestown Island folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 6)
  - State House excavations site drawings (2) (from Plans: State House folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 7)
  - Preliminary drawing of Third State House reconstruction (2) (from Plans: State House folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 7)
  - Road maps of Williamsburg (3) (from Plans: Williamsburg Traffic Flow folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 8)
  - Traffic flow and capacity maps (2) (from Plans: Williamsburg Traffic Flow folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 8)
  - Layout of Court of Welcome area (from Queen's Visit: Schedule folder) (Drawer 1, Folder 9)
  - Map of Virginia, districts color-coded; Department of Planning and Economic Development, 1955 (Drawer 1, Folder 10)
- Oversize Material (Map Case OS-3)
  - Aeronautical chart of Norfolk area (from Charts folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - Topographical map of Surry (from Charts folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - Hydrographic map above Jamestown (from Charts folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - Hydrographic map below Jamestown (from Charts folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - Map of proposed hydraulic fill site (from Charts folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - Drawings of foundations of Green Spring (2) (from Plans: Green Spring folder) (Drawer 12, Folder 2)